{"data":[{"question":"He was in a traffic jam,___ made him late for his appointment.","a":"that","b":"which","c":"what","d":"how","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Which: used, after a comma in writing, to add more information about the thing, situation, or event you have just mentioned ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Choose _________ you think is suitable.","a":"which","b":"that","c":"whom","d":"what","answer":"4","explain":"- \"\"Whom\"\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n-That\u00a0normally refers to\u00a0things\u00a0but it may refer to a class or type of person. \n- What: used to introduce a clause about something that is or was not known or not certain \n+ What is preferred when the number of choices is unlimited - That: used after verbs, nouns, and adjectives to introduce a clause which shows what someone says or thinks, or states a fact or reason \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n+We prefer which when the number of choices is limited","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I gave him a warning,___ he turned a deaf ear.","a":"of what","b":"for which","c":"to that","d":"to which","answer":"4","explain":"-That\u00a0normally refers to\u00a0things\u00a0but it may refer to a class or type of person. \n- What: used to introduce a clause about something that is or was not known or not certain \n+ What is preferred when the number of choices is unlimited - That: used after verbs, nouns, and adjectives to introduce a clause which shows what someone says or thinks, or states a fact or reason \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n+We prefer which when the number of choices is limited","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"This dictionary, the few pages ___ are missing, is of no use.","a":"among which","b":"of which","c":"in which","d":"to which","answer":"2","explain":"\n - A few pages of which= a few pages of this dictionary","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The audience were utterly astonished at the fluency ___ the little girl made her first English speech.","a":"with which","b":"by which","c":"of which","d":"in what","answer":"1","explain":"\n- With which: the fluency the little girl made with her... ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The sick man ___ sake you are doing all this work ought to be very grateful to you.","a":"for whom","b":"for whose","c":"of whom","d":"of whose","answer":"2","explain":"\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to) \n- Doing all this work for","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I was so eager to go away that when I stood in the hall, ready to leave, I did not even think of saying good-bye to the boys and girls ___ I had eaten and slept and lived for so many weeks.","a":"by whom","b":"of whom","c":"with whom","d":"with which","answer":"3","explain":"\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to) \n- With whom: I had eaten and slept and lived with the boys and girls for so many years","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"___ comes back first is supposed to win the prize.","a":"Those who","b":"Anyone","c":"No one","d":"Whoever","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Whoever: used to say that it does not matter who does something, is in a particular place","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Give this prize to ___ composition is thought excellent.","a":"whoever","b":"whosever","c":"whomever","d":"whatever","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Whosever: the one or ones belonging to whomever","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"This is the very boy ___ parents were killed last year.","a":"who","b":"that","c":"whose","d":"whom","answer":"3","explain":"\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to) \n- That normally refers to things but it may refer to a class or type of person.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}